Combination CV Sample

PETER SMITH

Washington DC, USA peter@smith.com (+21) 334111

SUMMARY

Dependable **General Office Worker** with more than 10 years of transferable experience. Proven clerical, customer service, and communication skills in a variety of settings. Upbeat, positive attitude with a history of producing quality results and satisfied customers. Computer literate.

SELECTED SKILLS

General Office

- · Organized and implemented group activities in an efficient manner
- Scheduled appointments and assured timely arrival
- Maintained accurate financial records, and paid all invoices on time
- Answered phones and took accurate messages
- Prepared reports and created documents using MS Word and WordPerfect
- · Located desired information using the Internet

Customer Service

- · Welcomed customers and visitors in a friendly and courteous manner
- Provided customers/clients with desired information in a timely manner
- Listened, calmed, and assisted customers with concerns
- Established friendly and lasting relationships

Communication

- Utilized Internet email as an effective communication tool
- · Answered phones in a courteous and professional manner
- Established rapport with diverse individuals and groups
- Demonstrated ability to express ideas in a team environment and influence action

Professional Experience:

The Store, Birmingham, UK 2005 - present

Sales Manager

- Responsible for team of 10 staff.
- Duties included buying stock, promoting lines, organising sales and promotions, dealing with customers and cashing up daily takings.

The Mall, Liverpool, UK

2001 - 2005

Assistant Manager

- Involved in purchasing new lines and stock.
- Handled cash and credit purchasing transactions.
- In charge of store when manager absent taking on full responsibilities.
- Dealing with customers, helping with purchases and finding solutions for complaints.

RELATED VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

General Onice volunteer Salvation Anni –, AZ 1333-200.	General Office Volunteer	Salvation Armv –. AZ	1999-2001
--	--------------------------	----------------------	-----------

Elected Secretary Parent Teachers Association , AZ 2001-1997

Event Coordinator Neighborhood Involvement Program – 3 Years

EDUCATION

2010- 2011 International Hellenic University, Thessaloniki ,Greece

MSc in Management

Dissertation Thesis: "....."

1992 – 1994 Anytown College, Thessaloniki, Greece

Bachelor in Economics

REFERENCES

Available upon request